Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1944-2003 (bulk 1959-1994) MS 3009-RG 6
New-York Historical Society
- Series I.A. Editor-in-Chief Hedley Donovan Files, 1948-1989 (bulk 1959-1979); 56.5 Linear feet in 57 record cartons
  - Subseries I.A.5. Subject Files, 1948-1983; 35 Linear feet in 35 record cartons
    - Fraternities, 1964 (Offsite-box 733, Folder 38)
    - Gaylord A. Freeman, Jr., 1966, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 733, Folder 39)
    - Forest Items, undated (Offsite-box 733, Folder 40)
    - Fuerbringer, Otto, 1962-1975 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 1-2)
    - Furniture: Office, 1970 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 3)
    - Furth, Bill, 1962 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 4)
    - Furth, Bill: Report on Armour Trip, undated (Offsite-box 734, Folder 5)
    - FYI, 1948, 1958, 1968, 1973 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 6)
    - F: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 7-9)
    - Galbraith: The Affluent Society, 1958-1959, undated (Offsite-box 734, Folder 10)
    - Gardner, John, 1967-1978 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 11)
    - Gart, Murray, 1975-1978 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 12)
    - Germans, 1973 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 13)
    - Gold, Jay, 1969-1974 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 14)
    - Governmental Affairs Institute Advisory Committee, 1960 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 15)
    - Graham, Mrs. Philip, 1960-1968, 1975 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 16)
    - Graves, Ralph, 1968-1979, undated (Offsite-box 734, Folder 17)
    - Griffin, Tom, 1962-1979 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 18)
    - Grover, Allen, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 19)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Corporate Editor, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 20)
    - Grunwald, Henry, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 21)
    - The Guild, 1961-1978 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 22)
    - The Guild [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 6)
    - G: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 734, Folder 23-27)
    - Hall, Lee project, 1970 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton, Denis, 1971 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 2)
    - Harding, Harry, 1968 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 3)
    - Hardy, Jerry, 1965-1969 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 4)
    - Harlem Walking Tour, 1968 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 5)
    - Harris, Bill, 1971 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 6)
    - Lou Harris Associates, 1968-1976 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 7)
    - Heard, Alexander, 1968-1977 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 8)
    - Heilperin, Michael, 1959-1971 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 9-10)
    - Heiskell, Andrew, 1960-1978 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 11-12)
    - Hodgins, Eric, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 13)
    - Hoffman, Paul, 1960-1966, 1975 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 14)
    - Horner, Matina, 1974 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 15)
    - House & Home, 1960-1964 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 16)
    - Hudson Institute, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 17)
    - Hughs, John Emmet, 1959-1964 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 18)
    - Hughes Project, 1973 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 19)
    - Hughes, Howard: Clifford Irving Matter, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 20)
    - Hunt, George, 1962-1977 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 21)
    - Hunt, George: TV experiment, 1970 (Offsite-box 735, Folder 22)
    - H: Miscellaneous, 1960-1979 (Offsite-box 735-736)
    - Impeachment Hearings by the Judiciary Committee: The New York Times: 7/22-7/31, 1974 (Offsite-box 736, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Congress, 1974 (Offsite-box 736, Folder 5)
    - Investigative Matters, 1970 (Offsite-box 736, Folder 6)
    - Invitations, Accepted, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 736, Folder 7)
    - Invitations regretted to speak, appear, write, join, etc., 1964-1979 (Offsite-box 736-737)
    - Invitations regretted to serve on committees, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 737, Folder 5-6)
    - Invitations regretted, 1960-1971 (Offsite-box 737-738)
    - I: Miscellaneous, 1965-1977 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 3)
    - Jackson, C.D., 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 4)
    - James, Sidney L., 1969-1979 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 5)
    - Japan, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 6)
    - Jessup, John, 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 7)
    - Job Definition & Methods, 1959 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 8)
    - Journalism: Mission of Spring: Definitions by Time Edit Staff, 1971 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 9)
    - J: Miscellaneous, 1960-1979 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 10)
    - Keogh, James, 1968-1977 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 11)
    - Khrushchev Remembers: Vol. I, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 12)
    - Khrushchev Remembers: Vol. II, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 13)
    - Khrushchev Remembers: Vol. I: Thank you letters, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 14)
    - Khrushchev Remembers: Vol. II: Thank you letters, 1974 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 15)
    - Kissinger, Henry A., 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 16)
    - Korean Prime Minister Chung's Visit: March 12-17, 1967 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 17)
    - Korn, Jerry, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 18)
    - Kosygin, Alexi, 1969 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 19)
    - K: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 20-22)
    - LaGuerre, Andre, 1961-1974 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 23)
    - LaGuerre, Andre [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 7)
    - LaLiberties, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 24)
    - Larson, Roy, 1959-1962, 1969, 1976-1979 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 25)
    - Lasker Medical Journalism Awards, 1967-1969 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 26)
    - Leisure and Purpose, 1955 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 27)
    - Lessing, Larry memo, 1965 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 28)
    - Leadership Conference: September 26-27, 1976 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 29-30)
    - Letters of Recommendation and Introduction [RESTRICTED], 1965-1979 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 8-10)
    - Letters to Trudi Lanz, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 738, Folder 31)
    - Liberalism, Classical, Weakness: Notes: Miscellaneous, undated (Offsite-box 738, Folder 32)
    - Life Magazine, 1978-1979, undated (Offsite-box 738, Folder 33)
    - Lindsay, Mary and John, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 1)
    - Linen, James, 1961-1977 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 2)
    - Links Club Meetings, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 3)
    - Linowitz, Sol M. [RESTRICTED], 1970-1976 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 11)
    - Lists, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 4)
    - Lists: Academic Talent, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 5)
    - Look Magazine, 1971 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 6)
    - Lubar, Bob, 1970-1974 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 7)
    - Luce, Henry III, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 8)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1978 November 2: Dinner for Ralph and Eleanor Graves: Brussels (Offsite-box 739, Folder 9)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1978 June 21: Tom Griffith 35th Anniversary Dinner: "21" Club (Offsite-box 739, Folder 10)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1977 April 19: Cocktail party for Dr. James Hester (Offsite-box 739, Folder 11)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1976 December 20: Cocktail Party: Boston (Offsite-box 739, Folder 12)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1976 November 9: National Audubon Society dinner honoring John Oakes (Donovans did not attend) (Offsite-box 739, Folder 13)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1976 September 20: Dick Seamon Retirement Party (Offsite-box 739, Folder 14)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1976 April 29: David Truman, President of Mount Holyoke College (Offsite-box 739, Folder 15)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1975 September 17: Otto Fuerbringer Retirement: Dinner at "21" (Offsite-box 739, Folder 16)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1974 February 26: Lunch: Egyptian Ambassador (Offsite-box 739, Folder 17)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1974 February 13: Lunch: Pakistan's Ambassador to the United Nations: Time & Life Building (Offsite-box 739, Folder 18)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1973 September 24: Lunch: Prime Minister of Pakistan: Time & Life Building (Offsite-box 739, Folder 19)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1971-1975: Hedley Donovan Pourings (Offsite-box 739, Folder 20)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1971 March 15: Norman Mailer Luncheon (Offsite-box 739, Folder 21)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1971 April 15: Donovan Lunch for Norman Mailer (Offsite-box 739, Folder 22)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1969: Cocktails with Staff (Offsite-box 739, Folder 23)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1968 June: Time Dinner (Offsite-box 739, Folder 24)
    - Lunches and Dinners: 1961: Soviet Journalist Dinner (Offsite-box 739, Folder 25)
    - Lunches and Dinners, 1964-1979 (Offsite-box 739-740)
    - Lunches: Executive, 1971 (Offsite-box 739, Folder 33)
    - L: Miscellaneous, 1960-1979 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 4-7)
    - Magazine Comparisons, 1960 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 8)
    - Magazine Publishers Association, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 9)
    - Management, Art of, 1957, undated (Offsite-box 740, Folder 10)
    - Manley, Joan, 1971-1978 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 11)
    - March of Time & Henry Cabot Lodge, 1961-1965 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 12)
    - Markham, Felix, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 13)
    - McManus, Jason [empty], undated (Offsite-box 740, Folder 14)
    - Memos to the Editors, 1965-1978 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 15-16)
    - Menu Files, 1968, undated (Offsite-box 740, Folder 17)
    - Meyers, Joan, 1967-1972 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 18)
    - Missiles, 1959 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 19)
    - Mondadori, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 20)
    - Money: General Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Offsite-box 740, Folder 21-22)
    - Money: Circulation Study: October, 1976 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 1)
    - Money: Prospectus: 1971 July 9 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 2)
    - Money: Readership Research: D. Ferenbaugh: September, 1973 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 3)
    - Money: A Study of Attitudes and Reactions, 1973 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 4)
    - Moore, M.T., 1965 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 5)
    - Morale Committee, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 6)
    - More Magazine, 1976 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 7)
    - Morgue Rules, 1971 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 8)
    - Moses, Robert E., 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 9)
    - Moyers, Bill, 1974 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 10)
    - Murphy, Arthur, 1960, 1968 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 11)
    - Murphy, Charles J.V., 1960-1976 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 12)
    - M: Miscellaneous, 1960-1979 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 13-17)
    - NATO, 1958-1959, 1966 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 18-19)
    - NATO: Tom Griffith memo and comments, 1966 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 20)
    - Nason, John, 1966 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 21)
    - National Forest Products, 1970 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 22)
    - National News Council, 1973 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 23)
    - New Life Magazine [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 12)
    - New Magazines Ideas, 1971-1978 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 24)
    - New Magazines, 1973 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 25)
    - New Magazines: British Sports Illustrated, 1974 (Offsite-box 741, Folder 26-27)
    - New Magazines: Camera Month, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 1-3)
    - New Magazines: International Sports Illustrated, 1974 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 4)
    - New Magazines: Life: Special Issues, 1973-1977 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 5-6)
    - New Magazines: Life: Special Issue on Israel, 1973 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 7)
    - New Magazines: Living With Science, 1979 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 8)
    - New Magazines: New Life Magazine, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 9)
    - New Magazines: Spirit Magazine, 1973 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 10)
    - New Magazines: Us, 1976 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 11)
    - New Magazines: View, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 742, Folder 12-14)
    - New Magazines: Women's Magazine, 1973-1977, undated (Offsite-box 742-743)
    - Newspaper Division, 1970 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 3)
    - Newsweek, 1965, 1972-1976 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 4)
    - New York Graphic Society, 1966 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 5)
    - Nickel, Herman, 1976-1978 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 6)
    - Nieman Fellows, 1960-1976 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 7)
    - Norton-Taylor, Duncan, 1959-1960, 1972 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 8)
    - Not Solicited Correspondence, 1972-1977, undated (Offsite-box 743, Folder 9)
    - N: Miscellaneous, 1960-1978 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 10-11)
    - Oakes, John, 1965-1977 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 12)
    - Oberdorfer, Don, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 13)
    - Orbis, 1961 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 14)
    - Organization, Theory of the Large, 1958 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 15)
    - Organization vs Freedom, Creativity, 1959 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 16)
    - Outside Writing, 1964 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 17)
    - Overseas Press Club, 1964-1973 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 18)
    - O: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 19)
    - Pace, Frank, 1963 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 20)
    - Pacem in Terris, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 21)
    - Pacem in Terris II, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 22)
    - Paine, Del, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 23)
    - Parker, Sandy, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 24)
    - Pauling, Dr. Linus, 1963 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 25)
    - Payola, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 26)
    - People: Background Analysis: 1973 October 12 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 27)
    - People: General Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 743, Folder 28-30)
    - People: Study: Target Public Attitudes Towards People by Cambridge Marketing Group: 1974 November (Offsite-box 744, Folder 1)
    - People: Awareness and Purchasing Study: 1976 July (Offsite-box 744, Folder 2)
    - People: Subject Survey by Cambridge Marketing Group: 1976 July (Offsite-box 744, Folder 3)
    - People heard from, 19651972 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 4-5)
    - People Hedley Donovan has seen, 1963-1972 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 6)
    - Personnel, 1960-1972 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 7)
    - Personnel: Affirmative Action Program, 1975 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 8)
    - Personnel: Alcoholism, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 9)
    - Personnel: Brumbaugh Memo, 1964 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 10)
    - Personnel: Cards, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 11)
    - Personnel: Compensation Survey, 1961 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 12)
    - Personnel: Donovan Scholars, 1961-1972 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 13)
    - Personnel: Editorial, 1959-1962 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 14-15)
    - Personnel: Guild, 1967-1973 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 16)
    - Personnel: Job Applications, 1973, undated (Offsite-box 744, Folder 17)
    - Personnel: Management Meetings, 1961-1969 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 18)
    - Personnel: Minorities (Trent), 1970-1978 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 19)
    - Personnel: Plans and Policies, 1961 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 20)
    - Personnel: New Salary Compensation Program, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 21)
    - Personnel: Salaries, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 22)
    - Personnel: Salaries & Raises, 1974 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 23)
    - Personnel: Rhodes Scholar: Summer Program, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 24)
    - Personnel: Salary and Stock Information: Separate Divisions, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 25)
    - Personnel: Salary Reviews, 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 744, Folder 26)
    - Personnel: Staff Announcements, 1960-1979 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 1-9)
    - Personnel: Staff Evaluations, 1976 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 10)
    - Personnel: Bob Steed, 1975 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 11)
    - Personnel: Summer, 1963 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 12)
    - Personnel: Time Edit Staff: 1962 February (Offsite-box 745, Folder 13)
    - Petitions and Responses, 1970 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 14)
    - Phillip Morris, 1967 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 15)
    - Picture Collection, 1975 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 16)
    - Picture Policy, 1973 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 17)
    - Pioneer Papers, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 18)
    - Prentice, P. I., 1962-1969 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 19)
    - Population, 1959 (Offsite-box 745, Folder 20)
    - Postal Rates, 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 745-746)
    - Postal Service, 1975 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 2)
    - Preservation: Historical Buildings, Natural Beauty, 1959, undated (Offsite-box 746, Folder 3)
    - Price Commission, 1972 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 4)
    - Printing, 1959 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 5)
    - Public Interest, 1959 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 6)
    - Pullen, Wes, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 7)
    - Purtell, 1962-1963, undated (Offsite-box 746, Folder 8)
    - P: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 9-13)
    - Q: Miscellaneous, 1967 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 14)
    - Rate Cards, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 15)
    - Random House, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 16)
    - Reader's Digest, 1962-1975 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 17)
    - Reading Project, 1975-1976 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 18)
    - Reception Center, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 19)
    - Reporter's Committee for freedom of the press, 1973 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 20)
    - Requests for Autographs, Pictures, etc., 1966-1976 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 21)
    - Requests: For Money, 1965-1973 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 22)
    - Research projects, etc.: Background, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 746, Folder 23)
    - Research: Africa, 1976 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 1)
    - Research: Aid, Foreign and arms, 1976 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 2)
    - Retirement, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 3)
    - Ridgefield, 1961 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 5)
    - Ross, Norm, 1968-1977 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 6)
    - Rostow, Eugene V., 1971-1976 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 7)
    - Romanians, undated (Offsite-box 747, Folder 8)
    - Rowan, Roy, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 9)
    - Rowohlt Verlag, Gesellschaft, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 10)
    - Rukeyser, William, 1974-1978 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 11)
    - R: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 12-15)
    - Sa___ Views: Right of Center, 1969 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 16a)
    - Sabin, Dr. Albert, 1968 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 16b)
    - Sample letters, 1964-1978 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 17)
    - Schriever, B.A., 1968 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz Article, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 19)
    - Seligman, Dan, 1969-1977 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 20)
    - Shepley, Jim, 1959-1970 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 21)
    - Sider, Don, 1972 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 22)
    - Sidey, Hugh, 1974-1979 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 23)
    - Silberman, Charles, 1966-1978 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 24)
    - Silver Burdett, 1966 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 25)
    - Simmons, G., 1966-1968 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 26)
    - Sinatra, Frank, 1969 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 27)
    - Smith, Edgar, 1960-1973 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 28)
    - Solberg, Carl, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 29)
    - Space, 1959 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 30)
    - Speeches, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 31)
    - Sports Illustrated: Appraisal of Editors, undated (Offsite-box 747, Folder 32)
    - Sports Illustrated: Art, 1960, undated (Offsite-box 747, Folder 33)
    - Sports Illustrated: Articles, 1959-1960, 1973, undated (Offsite-box 747, Folder 34)
    - Sports Illustrated: Audience, undated (Offsite-box 747, Folder 35)
    - Sports Illustrated: Hank Brennan, 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 36)
    - Sports Illustrated: Budgets, 1960-1962, 1970 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 37)
    - Sports Illustrated: Hedley Donovan criticism of, 1961-1963, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 38)
    - Sports Illustrated: Dinner for Terrell & Cave: 1974 November 25 (Offsite-box 747, Folder 39)
    - Sports Illustrated: Execution Troubles, undated (Offsite-box 747, Folder 40)
    - Sports Illustrated: Furth, Bill, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 1-2)
    - Sports Illustrated: Formula, etc, Points, 1960 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 3)
    - Sports Illustrated: The General Problem, undated (Offsite-box 748, Folder 4)
    - Sports Illustrated: Goren Book, 1961 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 5)
    - Sports Illustrated: Promotion, 1959 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 6)
    - Sports Illustrated: Possible memo to Luce, undated (Offsite-box 748, Folder 7)
    - Sports Illustrated: Snyder Schedules, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 8)
    - Sports Illustrated: Miscellaneous Staff Information, 1957-11959, 1971 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 9)
    - Sports Illustrated: Story Ideas, 1974 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 10)
    - Sports Illustrated: Strategy Memos, 1962 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 11)
    - Sports Illustrated: Subscriber's Attitudes, 1964 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 12)
    - Sports Illustrated: General, 1958-1978 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 13-18)
    - Staff Gatherings: Auditorium, 1971 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 19)
    - Statements (Shepley-Heiskell-Freeman): "The State of the Economy in the 70s", 1971 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 20)
    - Steele, John, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 21)
    - Stillman, Stanley, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 22)
    - Stolley, Richard, 1978 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 23)
    - Strike: Post-strike memos from all MEs: June, 1976 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 24)
    - Strike: Post-strike memos: Misc.: June, 1976 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 25)
    - Subscriptions, 1959-1975 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 26)
    - Supreme Court: Stories in Time: 1972 January 10-1973 February 26, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 27)
    - Synanon, 1969-1978 (Offsite-box 748, Folder 28)
    - Synanon [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 13)
    - Synanon: Deposition [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Offsite-box R10, Folder 14-15)
    - S: Miscellaneous, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 748-749)
    - Temple, Arthur, 1976 (Offsite-box 749, Folder 6)
    - Thielicke, Dr. Helmut, 1963-1970 (Offsite-box 749, Folder 7)
    - Thompson, Edward K., 1963-1978 (Offsite-box 749, Folder 8)
    - Tibby, Jack, 1976-1977, undated (Offsite-box 749, Folder 9)
    - Time and Life Building, 1960 (Offsite-box 749, Folder 10)
    - Time: General, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 749-750)
    - Time: Australian Edition, 1970 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 2)
    - Time: Canadian Edition, 1962-1975 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 3-4)
    - Time: European Edition, 1972-1977 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 5)
    - Time: Pacific, 1973 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 6)
    - Time: Man of the Year, 1975-1977 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 7-8)
    - Time: 40th Anniversary Dinner: 1963 May 6 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 9-11)
    - Time: 50th Anniversary Dinner: Waldorf-Astoria: 1973 October 22 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 12)
    - Time Magazine: Bicentennial Articles by Heads of Foreign Countries, 1976 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 13)
    - Time and the Blind, 1959-1960, undated (Offsite-box 750, Folder 14)
    - Time: Board of Economists, 1969 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 15-16)
    - Time Inc: Canada Commission Hearings, 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 17)
    - Time: Color Projects, 1960, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 18)
    - Time Magazine: Complaints, 1961-1972 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 19)
    - Time, Critiques of, 1959 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 20)
    - Time: Edit closing reports, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 21)
    - Time: Edit Task Force Report: 1976 Jan. 7 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 22)
    - Time: Editorial headcount and expenses, 1969 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 23)
    - Time: Essay & Correspondence: Hedley Donovan: 1975 May 19 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 24)
    - Time: European News Tour, 1964 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 25)
    - Time: Establishment Cover Story, 1970 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 26)
    - Time: Foreign Affairs, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 27)
    - Time: Grunwald Staff Memos, 1976 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 28)
    - Time: Minnesota Cover Story, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 750, Folder 29)
    - Time: Mobil Flap: March, 1971 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 1)
    - Time: New Design: Summer, 1977 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 2)
    - Time: Researcher Headcount, 1975 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 3)
    - Time: Special Issue: Russian Revolution, 1977 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 5)
    - Time: Survey and Studies, 1975 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 5-6)
    - Time: Leadership Special Section: 1974 July 15 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 7)
    - Time: Letters, 1973-1974 (Offsite-box 751, Folder 8)